The boxes flying down the
line at this
盒子飞下
在此行
2.3-million-square-foot
distribution center are
230万平方英尺
配送中心
sorted, scanned and labeled,
then loaded into trucks
进行分类、扫描和贴标签，
然后装入卡车
destined for the shelves of
the country's biggest
运往货架
该国最大的
retailer. Walmart employs
more people than any other
零售商。沃尔玛员工
比世界上任何其他公司都拥有更多的员工
company in the world, and
90% of Americans live within
公司，并且
90% 的美国人居住在距离沃尔玛 10 英里的范围内
10 miles of a Walmart. Yet
when it comes to e commerce,
。然而
在电子商务方面，
Amazon is the clear leader
with 39.5% of the market
亚马逊是明显的领导者
与沃尔玛相比，市场份额为 39.5%
share compared to Walmart's
7%. And with the global
7%。随着全球
pandemic helping shift
shoppers' behavior for good,
疫情的帮助转变
购物者的良好行为，
dominance in online shopping
is now paramount. Last year,
在线购物的主导地位
现在是最重要的。去年，
people spent more on Amazon
then at Walmart for the
人们在亚马逊上的花费更多
然后是第一次在沃尔玛
first time. Now Walmart's
got a new playbook and new
第一次。现在是沃尔玛的
有了新的剧本和新的
leadership as it races to
catch up.
领导力
赶上。
We have 4,700 locations
across the U.S. and if the
我们有 4,700 个地点
在美国各地，如果
store acts like a
fulfillment center, we can
商店就像一家
运营中心，我们可以
send those items the
shortest distance in the
将这些商品发送至
fastest time.
用时最短的距离。
Over the past few years,
Walmart's built more than 30
在过去的几年里，
沃尔玛建了超过30个
warehouses like this, some
with robots and people,
这样的仓库，有一些
与机器人和人类一起，
entirely dedicated to
fulfilling online orders.
完全致力于
履行在线订单。
Workers at stores are also
picking and packing online
商店的工作人员也
在线分拣和包装
orders, as Walmart turns
dozens of stores into
订单，随着沃尔玛的转变
数十家商店进入
micro-fulfillment centers.
It's added membership
微型配送中心。
它增加了会员资格
program Walmart+ to compete
with Prime, invested heavily
计划 Walmart+ 参与竞争
与 Prime 合作，大力投资
in local delivery programs
in homes and with drones,
本地配送计划
在家里和用无人机，
and started packing and
shipping orders for
并开始打包和
为
third-party sellers as it
works to entice them to
第三方卖家发货的订单
努力吸引他们访问
Walmart.com.
Walmart.com。
I'd say assortment is the
linchpin to this plan and
我想说的是分类是
该计划的关键
then sellers are a means to
get to assortment.
然后卖家是一种手段
进入分类。
They're looking at Amazon's
market share saying how can
他们正在查看亚马逊的
市场份额说
we grow this market share?
We need more sellers. We
我们如何才能扩大这个市场份额？
我们需要更多的卖家。我们
need more selection.
需要更多选择。
Customers trust us for food
and consumables. They trust
顾客信任我们的食物
和消耗品。他们信任
us for general merchandise,
but they're looking for
我们的一般商品，
但他们正在寻找
every item that they could
think of. We want to make
他们能找到的所有物品
想到。我们希望
sure that we're able to do
that for them.
确保我们能够做到
CNBC went to Walmart
headquarters in Bentonville,
CNBC 去了沃尔玛
总部位于阿肯色州本顿维尔
Arkansas, for the first ever
public interview with
有史以来第一个
公开采访
Walmart's new head of
e-commerce Tom Ward to find
沃尔玛新任主管
电子商务 Tom Ward 寻找
out the truth behind his big
plans for catching Amazon
他的大生意背后的真相
计划赶上亚马逊
online.
在线。
Walmart was founded in 1962
by Sam Walton, growing to
沃尔玛成立于 1962 年
由 Sam Walton 创立，已发展到
nearly 2,000 stores by the
time Jeff Bezos founded
近 2,000 家商店
杰夫·贝索斯 (Jeff Bezos) 于 1994 年创立
Amazon in 1994. Despite its
in-store dominance, Walmart
亚马逊。
沃尔玛在店内占据主导地位
was notoriously slow to the
e-commerce game, not
众所周知，
电商游戏，而非
launching its third-party
marketplace until 2009. It
推出第三方
市场直到 2009 年。
didn't make real headway
until 2016, when Walmart
并没有取得真正的进展
直到 2016 年，沃尔玛
bought discount online
retailer Jet.com for $3.3
网上购买折扣
零售商 Jet.com 以 3.3 美元
billion, tapping co-founder
Mark Lore to lead
十亿美元收购联合创始人
Mark Lore 领导电子商务
e-commerce, where he stayed
until last year. In 2018, it
他留任的地方
直到去年。 2018年，
spent big to get into the
booming online market in
花费巨资进入
借助 Flipkart，印度在线市场蓬勃发展
India with Flipkart, and
also bought online fashion
还购买了在线时尚
brands like Bonobos and
Eloquii. Then in 2020,
Bonobos 和
埃洛基伊。然后在 2020 年，
Walmart shut down Jet.com,
although CEO Doug McMillon
沃尔玛关闭了 Jet.com，
尽管首席执行官 Doug McMillon
says he would buy it all
over again.
表示他会全部购买
You look at the trajectory
of our business, it changed
你看看轨迹
我们的业务发生了变化
when we made that
acquisition. The Walmart
当我们这样做时
获得。沃尔玛
brand really has extended to
reach all kinds of people:
品牌确实已扩展到
覆盖各类人群：
affluent customers, younger
customers, urban customers.
富裕客户、年轻客户
客户，城市客户。
We were going to need a
brand to be able to use to
我们需要一个
品牌能够用来
attract some of the brands
that did not yet want to be
吸引一些品牌
还不想出现在我们的商店中
in our stores.
。
Also in 2020, Walmart
partnered with Shopify to
同样在 2020 年，沃尔玛
与 Shopify 合作
bring thousands of
mom-and-pop sellers to
带来了数千
夫妻店卖家
Walmart's marketplace.
That's the term used to
沃尔玛市场。
这是用于区分由
来自
differentiate items sold by
third-party sellers from the
first-party merchandise
bought and sold by Walmart.
第一方商品的第三方卖家
由沃尔玛购买和销售。
2020 also saw the launch of
Walmart+ and Walmart
2020 年还推出了
Walmart+ 和 Walmart
Fulfillment Services to
rival Fulfilled by Amazon,
配送服务
竞争对手由亚马逊配送，
or FBA, but leveraging
stores and their built-in
或 FBA，但利用
商店及其内置
workforce to keep costs low.
劳动力以保持低成本。
Walmart's definitely like
doubling, tripling down on
沃尔玛'绝对喜欢
将其电子商务业务扩大一倍、三倍
their e-commerce business,
trying their best to take
尽最大努力夺走
market share away from
Amazon or catch up to them.
市场份额
亚马逊或赶上他们。
The truth is though, they
still have a long ways to
事实是，他们
还有很长的路要走
go.
去。
Last year, Walmart opened up
its marketplace to
去年，沃尔玛开业了
其市场面向
international sellers. This
summer, Walmart plus weekend
国际卖家。这
夏天，沃尔玛加周末
is happening for the first
time with exclusive online
第一次发生
享受独家在线时光
deals for members just like
Amazon's Prime Day. And in
会员优惠，就像
亚马逊的 Prime Day。
February, Tom Ward took over
Walmart's e-commerce
二月，Tom Ward 接任
沃尔玛的电子商务
division.
部门。
The nearest Walmart to your
customer is the one in their
距离您最近的沃尔玛
客户就是他们口袋里的人
pocket. It's also the
ultimate store. It should be
。这也是
终极商店。它应该是
an endless assortment. It
should be completely, you
无穷无尽的品种。它
应该完全，你
know, full of solutions for
whatever customers are
知道，充满了解决方案
无论客户正在寻找什么
looking for. And
increasingly, marketplace
。和
市场
sellers really help us do
that.
卖家越来越多地真正帮助我们做到这一点
We went to a bustling
conference for e-commerce
我们去了一个繁华的地方
电子商务会议
sellers in Las Vegas in
March that's usually
拉斯维加斯卖家
三月通常
dominated by Amazon chatter.
For the first time in the
以亚马逊聊天为主。
Prosper Show's seven-year
history, Walmart also had a
Prosper Show 七年来首次
历史上，沃尔玛也占有重要地位
major presence
主要存在
Because they're smart, and
they know that this show is
因为他们很聪明，和
他们知道这个展会是卖家的所在地
where the sellers are, and
they want to get a lot of
，并且
他们希望在网站上获得更多
more brands on the
Walmart.com channel.
更多品牌
Walmart.com 渠道。
It's the only other
platforms that it could
这是唯一的其他渠道
真正可以与之竞争的平台
really be competition to
Amazon.
亚马逊。
Michael Lebhar started
selling on Walmart seven
Michael Lebhar 开始
七年前在沃尔玛销售
years ago when he was just a
sophomore in high school.
几年前，当时他只是一名
高中二年级学生。
At first, my mom was not
happy because my whole room
一开始，我妈妈不是
很高兴，因为我的整个房间
was just a bunch of USPS
boxes.
只是一堆 USPS
盒子。
Now Lebhar says Walmart.com
is his primary platform for
现在 Lebhar 说 Walmart.com
是他的 Spawn Fitness 品牌的主要平台
his Spawn Fitness brand,
which he says did about $3.5
他说这带来了约 3.5 美元
million of sales on
Walmart.com last year,
百万美元的销售额
Walmart.com 去年
compared to under half a
million on Amazon.
相比之下，去年
亚马逊上百万美元。
On Walmart, our profit
margins too are so good.
在沃尔玛上，我们的利润
利润也很好。
Like people are always like
oh, Walmart's price
就像人们总是一样
哦，沃尔玛的价格
competitive. Which, you're
right. Like sometimes you're
很有竞争力。哪个，你是
正确的。就像有时您
not able to charge as much.
But on Amazon you're
无法收取那么多费用。
但在亚马逊上，您
spending so much more on
advertising, like you don't
花费更多
广告，就像你没有意识到
even realize you're, you're
down so much because of
甚至意识到你是，你是
因为
that.
那个而下降了很多。
The cost of advertising on
Amazon has increased, but
广告费用
亚马逊有所增长，但
people are always going to
do it because more than ever
人们总是会
这样做是因为比以往任何时候都更
before it seems, if you're
not advertising on Amazon,
在看起来之前，如果你是
不在亚马逊上做广告，
you're not going to get
seen.
您不会得到
As the leader, Amazon can
charge sellers more for ads,
作为领导者，亚马逊可以
向卖家收取更多广告费、
seller account support and
fulfillment services. Jaré
卖家帐户支持以及
履行服务。 Jaré
Buckley-Cox used to work at
Amazon and now helps lead
巴克利-考克斯曾经在
亚马逊现在帮助领先
Walmart Fulfillment
Services, which launched in
沃尔玛配送
服务于
2020. WFS hasn't yet raised
prices and unlike FBA,
2020 年推出。 WFS尚未筹集
价格，与 FBA 不同，
offers seller support for
free.
为卖家提供支持
免费。
Year over year, Walmart
fulfillment services grew
年复一年，沃尔玛
履行服务的 GMV 增长了
500% In GMV. We add sellers
every day. Our competitive
500%。我们添加卖家
每天。我们的竞争优势
advantage and what's drawing
sellers into the program is
优势及现状
卖家加入该计划的原因是
the fact that they believe
this is a marketplace that
他们相信
这是一个专为他们打造的市场
is built for them.
。
But for now, Walmart still
has about a tenth of the
但就目前而言，沃尔玛仍然
大约有十分之一的
sellers and a tenth the
value of merchandise that
卖家和十分之一的
Amazon has. Greg Mercer
founded seller software
亚马逊拥有的商品价值。格雷格·默瑟
创立了卖家软件
company Jungle Scout, which
tracks industry numbers with
公司Jungle Scout，该公司
通过定期对数千人进行调查来跟踪行业数据
regular surveys of thousands
of sellers.
的卖家。
The fact that there are
significantly less sellers
事实上，有
我认为沃尔玛上的卖家明显减少
on Walmart, I think creates
less competition. And the
竞争较少。
result of that is the
Walmart sellers typically
结果就是
沃尔玛卖家通常
have a more profitable
business than what Amazon
利润更高
业务比亚马逊
sellers do.
卖家所做的业务还要多。
Surveys earlier this year,
founded 95% of Walmart
今年早些时候的调查，
创立了 95% 的沃尔玛
sellers turn a profit,
compared to about 76% on
卖家实现盈利，
相比之下，
Amazon.
亚马逊上的这一比例约为 76%。
Five years ago, Amazon
sellers just wanted to be on
五年前，亚马逊
卖家只想进入亚马逊
Amazon, they didn't want to
go anywhere else. But that
亚马逊，但他们不想
去别的地方吧。但这个
story has changed. Most
Amazon sellers that I talk
故事已经改变了。最多
我谈论的亚马逊卖家
to talk about, how can I
diversify more?
谈论，我该如何
更加多元化？
About a year ago, we
estimated that there were
大约一年前，我们
估计有
75,000 Walmart sellers and
over the past year, we've
75,000 名沃尔玛卖家
在过去的一年里，我们已经
seen that number double to
about 150,000 Walmart
看到这个数字翻了一番
今天约有 150,000 名沃尔玛卖家
sellers today.
今天有卖家。
Lauren Stark runs business
strategy for mDesign, one of
Lauren Stark 负责经营业务
mDesign 策略，
the biggest home storage
brands on Amazon with a
最大的家庭存储之一
亚马逊上的品牌
total of $310 million in
online sales last year.
总销售额达 3.1 亿美元
去年在线销售。
MDesig started selling on
Walmart in 2019 and started
MDesig 开始在
沃尔玛于 2019 年开始
investing more there during
the pandemic.
在此期间加大投资
流行病。
Because everyone was at
home. So that's when we
因为每个人都在
家。这就是我们
really ramped up our
strategy to to go on to
真正提高我们的能力的时候
继续进入不同市场的策略
different marketplaces, and
specifically Walmart.
特别是沃尔玛。
Diversify the risk,
diversify the reward as
分散风险，
奖励多样化
well, and reach more
customers.
好吧，并达到更多
客户。
Stark says mDesign will
likely do about $5 million
Stark 表示 mDesign 将会
沃尔玛今年的销售额可能约为 500 万美元
in sales on Walmart this
year, compared to $280
相比之下，去年亚马逊上的销售额为 280 美元
million on Amazon last year.
百万美元。
We are seeing, you know,
really nice increases year
我们看到，您知道，
今年沃尔玛的销售额增长非常好
over year on Walmart.
去年沃尔玛的销售额同比增长。
Stark says Target has been
even more successful because
Stark 表示 Target 一直在
更加成功，因为
there's even less
competition. Only brands
更少
竞赛。仅限 Target 邀请的品牌
that are invited by Target
can sell on its site. In
可以在其网站上出售。
contrast, it's relatively
simple for anyone to start
相比之下，相对来说
任何人都可以轻松开始
selling on Amazon and
competition is cutthroat.
在亚马逊上销售
竞争是残酷的。
You can take you know some
stereotypical like saturated
你可以带你了解一些
像饱和的刻板印象
product on Amazon, like a
garlic press or something,
亚马逊上的产品，就像
压蒜器什么的，
where there's 200 of the
same thing. There's maybe
那里有 200 个
同样的事情。也许
like three people selling a
garlic press, for example,
就像三个人在卖一个
例如，Walmart.com 上的压蒜器
on Walmart.com.
。
But Walmart wants that to
change.
但沃尔玛希望这样做
更改。
We want assortment on the
platform. So again,
我们想要分类
平台。再次强调，
customers can come and find
anything that they're
客户可以来找
他们正在寻找的任何内容
looking for and get it
delivered in any means that
并获取
以任何方式交付
they want.
他们想要的。
Walmart is also adding
assortment by launching a
沃尔玛也在添加
通过推出
growing collection of its
own brands, especially in
不断增长的产品系列来丰富产品组合
自有品牌，尤其是
apparel and home, that
appear first online and
服装和家居领域，
首先出现在网上，
later in stores. But as
Walmart's third-party
随后出现在商店中。但作为
沃尔玛的第三方
assortment grows, so too
does the risk for bad actors
品种也在增加
不良行为者是否存在风险
like Mpow and Aukey, two
huge electronics sellers
例如 Mpow 和 Aukey，两个
大型电子产品销售商
doing nearly $1 billion in
sales that were kicked off
销售额近 10 亿美元
已开始销售
Amazon but remain active on
Walmart.
亚马逊但在
沃尔玛。
They kicked them off for
buying reviews. And I was
他们把他们踢了
购买评论。我很伤心
sad to see that Walmart
allowed Mpow and Aukey to
看到沃尔玛
允许 Mpow 和 Aukey
now sell on the .com
platform. So as positive as
现在在 .com 上销售
平台。因此，就像积极的
I am with Walmart, I'm a
little bit disappointed that
我在沃尔玛一样，我是
有点失望
they allowed those two
brands with their practices,
他们允许这两个人
品牌及其做法，
which according to the FTC,
is illegal to do. You can't
根据 FTC 的说法，
这样做是违法的。您无法
buy reviews.
购买评论。
Walmart says it looked into
the allegations and didn't
沃尔玛表示已调查
的指控，但没有
find the same behavior from
Mpow and Aukey on its site.
发现来自
Mpow 和 Aukey 在其网站上。
As it works to boost
selection, Walmart also
因为它可以促进
选择，沃尔玛还
opened its marketplace up to
international sellers last
开放其市场至
国际卖家去年
year.
一年。
We know that Amazon had a
big crackdown last summer on
我们知道亚马逊
去年夏天对虚假评论进行了严厉打击
fake reviews. I think it
primarily impacted Chinese
。我认为是
主要对中国卖家的影响最大
sellers the most. That,
combined with Walmart
。那，
与沃尔玛结合
allowing international
sellers, we saw like a huge
允许国际
卖家，我们看到了
uptick in the percent of
Chinese sellers on Walmart.
的百分比大幅上升
沃尔玛上的中国卖家。
Still, sellers say Walmart
remains more stringent than
不过，卖家说沃尔玛
仍然比亚马逊更严格
Amazon when it comes to
approving new sellers.
亚马逊
批准新卖家。
And we're really proud of
the track record of having
我们对此感到非常自豪
拥有高标准的卖家记录
high standards for sellers
to get vetted before they
在加入该计划之前接受审查
get on the program. And
we're going to continue
。和
我们将继续
that.
这样做。
Another big way Walmart is
enticing sellers, which
沃尔玛的另一大举措
吸引卖家，这是亚马逊无法比拟的
Amazon can't match, is the
opportunity to get products
获得产品的机会
onto thousands of
brick-and-mortar shelves.
成千上万的人
实体货架。
Because you know, each store
has to get so many cases in
因为你知道，每个商店
必须有这么多的箱子
stock. I mean it's like game
over. If you're just like a
库存。我的意思是这就像游戏
超过。如果您只是一个
private label seller, to be
able to have your product in
自有品牌卖家，
能够将您的产品放入
Walmart stores is like a
holy grail.
沃尔玛商店就像
圣杯。
Our product was like at one
point, the number one in the
我们的产品就像是
点，在 Walmart.com 的
category on Walmart.com. So
we got an email from a
类别中排名第一。所以
我们收到一封来自
Walmart buyer being like,
you know, would you be
沃尔玛买家的电子邮件，内容如下：
您知道吗
interested in more talks?
对更多演讲感兴趣吗？
This year for the first
time, Walmart.com sellers
今年是第一次
当时，Walmart.com 卖家
were given first exclusive
access to a program called
获得了第一笔独家优惠
访问名为
Open Call, where sellers
pitch their products for
Open Call 的计划，卖家可以在其中
在沃尔玛商店中推销其产品
space on Walmart store
shelves. Some 2,000 sellers
空间
货架。大约 2,000 名卖家
applied.
申请了。
We've got a real mission to
increase assortment. So it
我们的真正使命是
增加品种。所以
just made sense that when
sellers are bringing
才有意义
卖家带来了
high-quality assortment, we
want to make that available
高品质的品种，我们
希望将其提供给我们的客户
to our customers in our
stores or online.
商店或网上。
Walmart's huge number of
stores also makes it the
沃尔玛的大量
商店也使其成为杂货店中无可争议的王者。
亚马逊于
undisputed king in grocery.
Amazon bought Whole Foods in
2017 and is trying to
disrupt the space by making
2017 年收购了 Whole Foods，并试图
将其中两个完全打乱
two of them entirely
cashierless. But Amazon.com
无收银员。但 Amazon.com
and Whole Foods each
accounted for less than 1.5%
和 Whole Foods 各有
占杂货市场的比例不到 1.5%
of the grocery market,
compared to Walmart's 18%.
与沃尔玛的 18% 相比。
Grocery is less profitable
than general merchandise,
杂货店的利润较低
比一般商品，
but the real power play is
for Walmart to get customers
但真正的威力发挥是
让沃尔玛吸引顾客
to fill their virtual
baskets with a mix of
填充他们的虚拟
混合了
grocery, general merchandise
and third-party items.
杂货、日用商品的篮子
和第三方商品。
Maybe you're shopping for
only a Walmart grocery store
也许您正在购买
只有沃尔玛杂货店
product, but at least that
traffic is there and it is
产品，但至少
交通就在那里，而且
heavy and a lot more
eyeballs on your products
很拥挤，而且更多
您的产品吸引了眼球
now.
现在。
Despite big upward trends
during the pandemic, both
尽管有很大的上升趋势
疫情期间，
Walmart and Amazon shares
fell sharply after Q1
沃尔玛和亚马逊均分享
第一季度
earnings were reported, as
supply chain issues and
收益报告后大幅下跌，因为
供应链问题和
increasing costs cut into
profits. But Walmart's long
不断增加的成本削减
利润。但沃尔玛长期以来
standing reputation as a
leader in low prices brings
作为
低价领先者带来了
an advantage right now, as
customers look for deals
现在的优势，因为
客户寻求通胀处于新水平的交易
with inflation at a new
40-year high.
40 年来新高。
To save you even more,
always low prices, always
为了为您节省更多，
始终低价，始终
Walmart.
沃尔玛。
As part of Walmart's
strategy to unite more parts
作为沃尔玛的一部分
联合其庞大零售帝国的更多部分
of its vast retail empire,
it recently combined what
的战略，
它最近将
used to be two separate
apps: one for Walmart's own
曾经是两个独立的部分合并在一起
应用程序：沃尔玛自有应用程序
goods, primarily grocery,
and another for its
商品，主要是杂货，
另一个用于其
third-party marketplace
products.
第三方市场
产品。
And wherever there's
friction in that process,
以及任何地方
在此过程中存在摩擦，
wherever there's two apps
and they should be one under
只要有两个应用程序
他们应该在一个屋顶下
one roof, we're now working
to remove all that friction.
一个屋顶，我们现在正在工作
消除所有这些摩擦。
Walmart+, launched in 2020,
also combines benefits for
Walmart+，于 2020 年推出，
还将为忠诚的杂货客户带来的好处与
loyal grocery customers with
online shopping perks. It's
网上购物福利。这是
Walmart's answer to Prime,
which Amazon launched all
沃尔玛对 Prime 的回应，
亚马逊早在 2005 年就推出了
the way back in 2005. Prime
now costs $139 a year for
所有 Prime。
现在每年只需 139 美元
benefits like one-day
shipping on more than 15
一天的福利
运送超过 15 件
million items, two-hour
grocery delivery in 2,000+
百万件商品，两小时
超过 2,000 个城市的杂货配送
cities, access to Prime Day
deals and Amazon's
享受 Prime Day
优惠和亚马逊
entertainment branch: Prime
Video, Amazon Music, Prime
娱乐分支：Prime
视频、亚马逊音乐、Prime
Reading, Prime Gaming and
Amazon Photos. Meanwhile,
阅读、Prime 游戏和
亚马逊照片。同时，
Walmart+ members pay $98 a
year for benefits like free
Walmart+ 会员每人支付 98 美元
年享受免费等福利
same-day delivery from
stores, free shipping on
当天送货
商店，免费送货
Walmart's own merchandise,
cashierless scan and go
沃尔玛自营商品，
无收银扫描即走
shopping at some stores, and
exclusive access to big
在一些商店购物，以及
独家参与大型
sales events like Walmart+
Weekend happening June 2-5
沃尔玛+等销售活动
今年周末发生在 6 月 2 日至 5 日
this year. And amid
record-high gas prices,
。而其间
创下历史新高的汽油价格，
Walmart just added extra
fuel discounts for its plus
沃尔玛刚刚增加了额外费用
其 plus 的燃油折扣
members who now get between
five and 10 cents off, not
现在介于
5 和 10 美分的折扣，不
only at Walmart's own pumps
but at some 14,000
仅限沃尔玛自有的泵
但约有 14,000 个
participating stations
including Exxon, Mobil,
参与电台
包括埃克森美孚、美孚、
Murphy and Sam's Club.
Walmart is also using its
墨菲和山姆俱乐部。
沃尔玛也在使用其
stores, and specifically
their proximity to
商店，特别是
作为优势，他们与客户的距离接近
customers, as an edge,
making big investments in
大力投资
speedy local delivery
programs.
快速本地交付
People are coming to us for
burgers and hotdogs, but
人们来找我们是为了
汉堡和热狗，但是
they can buy a brand new
smoker. They can get a whole
他们可以购买全新的
吸烟者。他们可以获得一整套
new swimsuit outfit. They
can get all of that under
新泳衣套装。他们
可以在一个屋顶、一个屋顶下获得所有这些
one roof, in one
application, in one place.
应用程序，在一个地方。
And we can fulfill it for
them with great speed thanks
我们可以完成它
感谢我们的足迹。
to our footprint.
Last year, Walmart launched
Express Delivery for
去年，沃尔玛推出了
快递
Walmart's own merchandise
that can reach your door in
沃尔玛自有商品
可以在
two hours or less for a $10
fee, with an additional fee
两小时或更短时间内送达您家门口，费用为 10 美元
费，额外费用
of at least $7.95 for
non-Walmart+ members. This
至少 7.95 美元
非沃尔玛+会员。这
doesn't include marketplace
items, but Ward says it
不包括市场
项目，但 Ward 表示它会为以下项目带来流量
drives traffic for those as
well.
好吧。
We can say to a customer:
Hey, you know, add these
我们可以对客户说：
嘿，您知道，请添加这些您想要的
items that you want this
evening. But if you want
项目
晚上。但如果您想要
that very specific item, we
can bring you that really
那个非常具体的项目，我们
也可以快速为您带来真正的
quickly as well.
。
Walmart has been ramping its
logistics operations since
沃尔玛一直在加大力度
物流运营
at least 2017, building 31
separate fulfillment centers
至少从 2017 年开始，31 号楼
独立的履行中心
devoted to e-commerce and
investing big in robotic
致力于电子商务和
大力投资机器人
e-commerce fulfillment,
following Amazon's lead.
电子商务履行，
跟随亚马逊的脚步。
Also like Amazon, Walmart
has independent drivers,
也喜欢亚马逊、沃尔玛
有独立的驱动程序，
what it calls its Spark
Network, who handle much of
它称之为 Spark
网络，负责处理大部分
the cumbersome, expensive
last-mile delivery.
繁琐、昂贵的事情
最后一英里送货。
We can activate drivers to
come and collect items and
我们可以激活司机
来收集物品并
deliver them to our
customer. But as the density
将它们运送到我们的
顾客。但随着密度
grows, the cost comes down.
增加，成本会下降。
So much so that last year,
Walmart started delivering
这么多，最后年，
沃尔玛开始为其他零售商配送商品
goods for other retailers in
a program that calls
一个调用
GoLocal.
GoLocal 的程序。
We've announced some really
exciting clients like the
我们已经宣布了一些真正的
令人兴奋的客户，例如
Home Depot and the Chico's
and others, including small
Home Depot 和 Chico’s
以及其他企业，包括小型
and medium businesses. And
what we're seeing is, as
和中型企业。和
我们所看到的是，
they share in our last-mile
capabilities, density
他们在我们的最后一英里分享
能力、密度
increases and the cost for
both of us goes down.
增加以及成本
我们俩都倒下了。
In Scottsdale, Arizona, Ward
says Walmart's completed
在亚利桑那州斯科茨代尔沃德
沃尔玛表示已通过 Cruise 完成了 5,000 次送货
5,000 deliveries with Cruise
autonomous vehicles.
自动驾驶汽车。
And this vehicle turns up
like magic outside and they
这辆车出现了
就像外面的魔法一样，他们
can grab it out of the
backseat. And then
可以从里面抓住它
后座。然后
increasingly, they can put
their return in the backseat
逐渐地，他们可以把
他们在后座返回
and send the car to the
Supercenter.
并将汽车送到
Supercenter。
Walmart also just announced
its expanding drone delivery
沃尔玛也刚刚宣布
到今年年底，其无人机交付规模将不断扩大
by the end of the year,
deploying them from 37
从 37 家商店部署它们
stores for a reach of 4
million households across
覆盖范围达到 4 家
万户家庭
Arizona, Arkansas, Florida,
Texas, Utah and Virginia.
亚利桑那州、阿肯色州、佛罗里达州、
德克萨斯州、犹他州和弗吉尼亚州。
Customers pay $3.99 for
items totaling up to 10
客户支付 3.99 美元
总重量不超过 10 磅的物品
pounds to be delivered by
drone in 30 minutes or more.
送货时间
无人机在 30 分钟或更长时间内。
In the same way that the
store is starting to act
以同样的方式
商店开始像履行中心一样运作
like a fulfillment center,
they're also starting to act
它们也开始像无人机发射一样
like a drone launch
delivery.
交付。
And there's the growing
popularity of buying online
而且数量不断增长
网上购物的流行
and picking up curbside, a
benefit Amazon can't rival.
和路边提货，
亚马逊无法匹敌的优势。
In some of these other areas
where Amazon Prime doesn't
在其他一些领域
Amazon Prime 没有
have like the two- and
three-, four-hour delivery,
像两个- 和
三、四小时送货，
but there's a Walmart store
nearby. You can be living in
但有一家沃尔玛商店
附近。您可以居住在
South Dakota or something
and you can get your product
南达科他州或其他地方
您可以在两三个小时内获得您的产品
in two or three hours,
whereas on Amazon, for Prime
而在亚马逊上，对于 Prime
it might take even more than
two days.
可能需要的时间甚至超过
两天。
While you can't currently
pick up third-party
虽然目前还不能
提货第三方
purchases at Walmart stores,
Buckley-Cox says items
在沃尔玛商店购买的商品，
巴克利-考克斯说项目
shipped with WFS will soon
be able to be forwarded to
将很快与 WFS 一起发货
能够转发到
stores for possible same-day
pickup or delivery. And
当天可能的商店
提货或送货。并且
while Amazon delivers
groceries to doorsteps and
当亚马逊送货时
杂货到门口
some items inside doors and
garages, Walmart has a
一些物品在门内和
车库，沃尔玛有一个
unique delivery program
straight into your fridge
独特的送货计划
直接放入冰箱
for $19.95 a month.
每月 19.95 美元。
It is so good for our
elderly customers that can't
这对我们来说非常好
无法出门的老年顾客
get out. Or if somebody has
broken an ankle or
或者如果有人有
脚踝骨折或者
something, broken a leg,
whatever, you know.
什么东西，腿骨折了，
不管怎样，你知道。
Thousands of full-time
Walmart associates like Mike
数千名全职
像迈克这样的沃尔玛员工
Edwards spend their days
filling up a fleet of fully
爱德华度过了他们的日子
为一支充满杂货的电动货车装满
electric vans with groceries
and general merchandise.
电动货车
和一般商品。
We don't step foot inside
the garage or the residence
我们不踏入内部
车库或住宅
without this on.
不戴此装置。
Then bringing it inside
people's homes and putting
然后将其带入室内
人们的家中，并将其放入冰箱
it away in the refrigerator.
Trusting a stranger to enter
。
信任陌生人进入您的家可能听起来很疯狂，
但该程序一直
your home may sound wild,
but the program has been
working well enough that
Walmart is rapidly expanding
运行良好，
沃尔玛正在迅速扩张
it to reach 30 million homes.
其覆盖 3000 万个家庭。
All of our associates wear
cameras on their vest, and
我们所有的员工都穿着
背心上的摄像头，以及交付的每个部分
被记录。他们无法
every part of the delivery
is recorded. They can't
actually access your home
until we confirm that their
实际访问您的家
直到我们确认他们的
camera is turned on and
working. And so as a
摄像头已打开并且
在职的。因此，作为
customer, if you place an
order and you are curious,
客户，如果您放置
订购并且您感到好奇，
you can watch the full experience.
您可以观看完整的体验。
InHome associates will also
take some returns back to
InHome 员工将还
为顾客将一些退货退回
Walmart for customers. And
Walmart is expanding the
沃尔玛。和
沃尔玛正在扩大
program to include alcohol
delivery and other highly
计划，将酒精饮料纳入其中
交付和其他高度
requested services it's not
ready to disclose.
要求的服务不是
准备好披露了。
And so they're like, oh my
gosh, you're here like, can
所以他们就像，哦天哪
天哪，你在这里，可以遛狗吗？
you walk the dog? Like, can
you take out the trash? It's
你可以遛狗吗？喜欢，可以
你倒垃圾吗？
like, how else can you help
me?
就像，您还能提供什么帮助
我？
While marketplace purchases
can't currently be delivered
市场购买时
目前无法送货上门
in home, it's another way
for Walmart to build loyalty.
送货上门，这是另一种方式
帮助沃尔玛建立忠诚度。
InHome offers a unique entry
point into Walmart for a lot
InHome 提供独特的入口
我们的很多客户
of our customers because we
have a pretty
都指向沃尔玛，因为我们
提供漂亮的
distinguishable offering on
the market. And now they're
独特的产品
市场。现在它们
on our website, and they're
shopping for groceries, but
出现在我们的网站上，并且它们
购买杂货，但
they're seeing other things
they might want to buy.
他们看到了其他东西
他们可能想购买。
They're seeing things
available in marketplace.
他们正在看到一些东西
市场上有售。
There are things that they
would never expect to see at
有些东西他们
永远不会想到会在
Walmart. And so now we have
them as a loyal customer in
沃尔玛看到。所以现在我们有
他们作为忠实的客户
a much more expansive and
much stickier way than we
一个更加广泛和
比我们预想的更有粘性
would have expected.
。
You know, they're not going
to catch up and be 50%
你知道，他们'我不去
明年迎头赶上并达到 50%
market share next year. But
if they continue to do the
市场份额。但
如果他们继续做
things that they're doing,
gradually they will continue
他们正在做的事情，
逐渐地，他们将继续
to eat more and more market
share, I believe.
吃越来越多的市场
分享，我相信。